No items found.

Need our logo?

[

Download Our Logo](https://cdn.prod.website-files.com/6372338e5477e047032b37a5/65081814c54363b3f1980d58_Shortcut_logo.png)[

Download Brand Pack](https://drive.google.com/file/d/1hngIivkf435EseNWSUbJqmYTltKCJrfz/view?usp=drive_link)[.svg)

Branding Guidelines](https://shortcut.com/branding)

Features

Key Features

[

Boards

See and track your work on Kanban boards](https://shortcut.com/product/boards)[

Reporting

Measure and review progress towards team goals](https://shortcut.com/product/reports)[

Roadmaps

See a big picture view of develpment workloads](https://shortcut.com/product/roadmap)[

Teams

Work crosss-functionally to get stuff done](https://shortcut.com/product/teams)[

Objectives

Align your work with company goals](https://shortcut.com/product/objectives)[

APIs

Connect shortcut to anything using our APIs](https://developer.shortcut.com/api/rest/v3)[

Docs

Connect your plans directly to your work](https://shortcut.com/product/docs)[

Automations

Let us do your busy work](https://shortcut.com/product/automations)[

Sprints

Manage work within a set period of time](https://shortcut.com/product/iterations-sprints)

Solutions for Teams

[

For Engineering

Use an issue tracker that’s helpful and not a hassle](https://shortcut.com/solutions/engineering)[

For Product

Track product backlogs and prioritize workloads](https://shortcut.com/solutions/product)[

For Design

Track designs, organize and prioritize workloads](https://shortcut.com/solutions/design)

Resources

Learn & Get Support

[

Help Center

Support and product documentation](https://help.shortcut.com/)[Schedule Demo

Meet 1:1 with our Customers Team](https://shortcut.com/demo)[

Release Notes

Find out about our latest releases](https://shortcut.com/release-notes)

Keep Up with Us

[

About Us](https://shortcut.com/about)[

Community & Events](https://shortcut.com/community)[

Security](https://shortcut.com/security)[

Shortcut Blog](https://shortcut.com/blog)

Our Customer Stories

[

How Thirty Madison scaled with Shortcut during explosive growth](https://shortcut.com/customer-stories/thirty-madison)

[

Dataiku uses Shortcut to greatly improve product prioritization and cross-team collaboration](https://shortcut.com/customer-stories/dataiku)

[All customer stories

](https://shortcut.com/customer-stories)

Switch now

[

Switch from Trello

Outgrown Trello? We provide more structure, options, and visibility for your growing software team.

Switch now

](https://shortcut.com/import/trello)

[

Switch from Jira

Suffering from Jiratation? Sync an existing Jira project with Shortcut or import your data from **Cloud** or **Server** instances with a few clicks.

Switch now

](https://shortcut.com/import/jira)

[

Switch from other tools

Switch now using our CSV Importer

Linear

ClickUp

Asana

Pivotal Tracker

Monday

\+ more...

Get started now

](https://shortcut.com/signup)

Privacy Policy
==============

**Effective as of June 15th, 2018**

We at Shortcut Software Company ("Shortcut," "we," "us," or "our") have created this privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy") because we want you to know how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Shortcut in connection with our Service which is made available to you through our Website (including mobile web) located at [https://www.shortcut.com](https://www.shortcut.com/), our App and our Platform (which may be accessed via the Website or App). By visiting our Website or using our Platform, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying [Terms of Service](https://www.shortcut.com/terms). Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service.

### Scope of this policy

The Website and the Platform are operated by Shortcut in the United States (US), and complies with US law. If you are located outside of the US, please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your home country, where the data protection laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

### EEA, UK, or Switzerland Residents

Natural persons located in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), the UK, or Switzerland, should review the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR") privacy notice for their specific rights, remedies, and other GDPR/Data Privacy Framework (DPF) related information [here](https://shortcut.com/gdpr-privacy).

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

* **Contact Information**
* **Payment Information**
* **From Your Activity**
* **From Cookies**

### Third-Party Analytics

We use one or more third–party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate your use of the Website, and the Platform, compile reports on activity (based on their collection of IP addresses, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, data and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Website and/or the Platform you visit, number of links clicked while on the Website and/or the Platform, search terms and other similar usage data), and analyze performance metrics. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By visiting the Website, and accessing and using the Services and/or the Platform, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. For more information on these third parties, including how to opt out from certain data collection, please visit the sites below. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Websites, Service or the Platform.

Google Analytics: [https://www.google.com/analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics)

Pendo: [https://www.pendo.io/privacypolicy/](https://www.pendo.io/privacypolicy/)

### CRM Data

We store our contact information within Salesforce CRM to help our sales and customer support team manage our relationships with current or prospective customers. Any personal data provided to/or collected by Salesforce will be used to provide our services in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Aggregate Data

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users and the Website, we might analyze your information in aggregate form to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our products and services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### Google API Disclosure

The Shortcut app uses Google APIs when you use your Google account to sign in via Google OAuth or when enabling the Google Drive Shortcut integration.

‍

Shortcut's use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.

### Business Transfers

In the event of a merger, dissolution or similar corporate event, or the sale of all or substantially all of our assets, we expect that the information that we have collected, including personal information, would be transferred to the surviving entity in a merger or the acquiring entity. All such transfers shall be subject to our commitments with respect to the privacy and confidentiality of such personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure to Public Authorities

We are required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including for the purpose of meeting national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose personal information to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas.

### Opt Out for Direct Marketing

You may opt out at any time from the use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, and/or transfer of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes by sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please allow us a reasonable time to process your request. You cannot opt out of receiving transactional or administrative e-mails related to our services or your requests for information or materials.

### Retention of Personal Information

We will retain your personal information in a form that identifies you only for as long as it serves the purpose(s) for which it was initially collected as stated in this Privacy Policy, subsequently authorized, or as allowed under applicable law.

### Delete Your Information

You may request access to and deletion of your personal data by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### How We Protect Your Information

We take very seriously the security and privacy of the personal information that it collects pursuant to this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we will implement reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of such data, and comply with applicable laws and regulations.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Website or the Service. If you are under 13, please do not give us any personal information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide us Personal Information without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that personal information from our databases.

### External Websites

The Website may contain links to third party websites. Shortcut has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other websites to which we provide links. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third party websites. You should check the applicable third party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Website or notify you via e-mail, at our option, as soon as they go into effect. By using the Website, App or the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍

‍

**Effective as of June 15th, 2018**

We at Shortcut Software Company ("Shortcut," "we," "us," or "our") have created this privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy") because we want you to know how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Shortcut in connection with our Service which is made available to you through our Website (including mobile web) located at [https://www.shortcut.com](https://www.shortcut.com/), our App and our Platform (which may be accessed via the Website or App). By visiting our Website or using our Platform, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying [Terms of Service](https://www.shortcut.com/terms). Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service.

### Scope of this policy

The Website and the Platform are operated by Shortcut in the United States (US), and complies with US law. If you are located outside of the US, please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your home country, where the data protection laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

### EEA, UK, or Switzerland Residents

Natural persons located in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), the UK, or Switzerland, should review the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR") privacy notice for their specific rights, remedies, and other GDPR/Data Privacy Framework (DPF) related information [here](https://shortcut.com/gdpr-privacy).

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

* **Contact Information**
* **Payment Information**
* **From Your Activity**
* **From Cookies**

### Third-Party Analytics

We use one or more third–party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate your use of the Website, and the Platform, compile reports on activity (based on their collection of IP addresses, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, data and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Website and/or the Platform you visit, number of links clicked while on the Website and/or the Platform, search terms and other similar usage data), and analyze performance metrics. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By visiting the Website, and accessing and using the Services and/or the Platform, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. For more information on these third parties, including how to opt out from certain data collection, please visit the sites below. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Websites, Service or the Platform.

Google Analytics: [https://www.google.com/analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics)

Pendo: [https://www.pendo.io/privacypolicy/](https://www.pendo.io/privacypolicy/)

### CRM Data

We store our contact information within Salesforce CRM to help our sales and customer support team manage our relationships with current or prospective customers. Any personal data provided to/or collected by Salesforce will be used to provide our services in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Aggregate Data

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users and the Website, we might analyze your information in aggregate form to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our products and services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### Business Transfers

In the event of a merger, dissolution or similar corporate event, or the sale of all or substantially all of our assets, we expect that the information that we have collected, including personal information, would be transferred to the surviving entity in a merger or the acquiring entity. All such transfers shall be subject to our commitments with respect to the privacy and confidentiality of such personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure to Public Authorities

We are required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including for the purpose of meeting national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose personal information to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas.

### Opt Out for Direct Marketing

You may opt out at any time from the use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, and/or transfer of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes by sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please allow us a reasonable time to process your request. You cannot opt out of receiving transactional or administrative e-mails related to our services or your requests for information or materials.

### Retention of Personal Information

We will retain your personal information in a form that identifies you only for as long as it serves the purpose(s) for which it was initially collected as stated in this Privacy Policy, subsequently authorized, or as allowed under applicable law.

### Delete Your Information

You may request access to and deletion of your personal data by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### How We Protect Your Information

We take very seriously the security and privacy of the personal information that it collects pursuant to this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we will implement reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of such data, and comply with applicable laws and regulations.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Website or the Service. If you are under 13, please do not give us any personal information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide us Personal Information without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that personal information from our databases.

### External Websites

The Website may contain links to third party websites. Shortcut has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other websites to which we provide links. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third party websites. You should check the applicable third party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Website or notify you via e-mail, at our option, as soon as they go into effect. By using the Website, App or the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍

‍

**Effective as of June 15th, 2018**

We at Shortcut Software Company ("Shortcut," "we," "us," or "our") have created this privacy policy (this "Privacy Policy") because we want you to know how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of Shortcut in connection with our Service which is made available to you through our Website (including mobile web) located at [https://www.shortcut.com](https://www.shortcut.com/), our App and our Platform (which may be accessed via the Website or App). By visiting our Website or using our Platform, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying [Terms of Service](https://www.shortcut.com/terms). Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service.

### Scope of this policy

The Website and the Platform are operated by Shortcut in the United States (US), and complies with US law. If you are located outside of the US, please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to, processed, maintained, and used on computers, servers, and systems located outside of your home country, where the data protection laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

### EEA, UK, or Switzerland Residents

Natural persons located in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), the UK, or Switzerland, should review the General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR") privacy notice for their specific rights, remedies, and other GDPR/Data Privacy Framework (DPF) related information [here](https://shortcut.com/gdpr-privacy).

### Information We Collect and How We Use It

* **Contact Information**
* **Payment Information**
* **From Your Activity**
* **From Cookies**

### Third-Party Analytics

We use one or more third–party analytics services (such as Google Analytics) to evaluate your use of the Website, and the Platform, compile reports on activity (based on their collection of IP addresses, Internet service provider, browser type, operating system and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, data and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of the Website and/or the Platform you visit, number of links clicked while on the Website and/or the Platform, search terms and other similar usage data), and analyze performance metrics. These third parties use cookies and other technologies to help analyze and provide us the data. By visiting the Website, and accessing and using the Services and/or the Platform, you consent to the processing of data about you by these analytics providers in the manner and for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. For more information on these third parties, including how to opt out from certain data collection, please visit the sites below. Please be advised that if you opt out of any service, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Websites, Service or the Platform.

Google Analytics: [https://www.google.com/analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics)

Pendo: [https://www.pendo.io/privacypolicy/](https://www.pendo.io/privacypolicy/)

### CRM Data

We store our contact information within Salesforce CRM to help our sales and customer support team manage our relationships with current or prospective customers. Any personal data provided to/or collected by Salesforce will be used to provide our services in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Aggregate Data

In an ongoing effort to better understand our users and the Website, we might analyze your information in aggregate form to operate, maintain, manage, and improve the Website. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may share this aggregate data with our affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our products and services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### Business Transfers

In the event of a merger, dissolution or similar corporate event, or the sale of all or substantially all of our assets, we expect that the information that we have collected, including personal information, would be transferred to the surviving entity in a merger or the acquiring entity. All such transfers shall be subject to our commitments with respect to the privacy and confidentiality of such personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

### Disclosure to Public Authorities

We are required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including for the purpose of meeting national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose personal information to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities or required by law or regulation including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas.

### Opt Out for Direct Marketing

You may opt out at any time from the use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes, and/or transfer of your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes by sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please allow us a reasonable time to process your request. You cannot opt out of receiving transactional or administrative e-mails related to our services or your requests for information or materials.

### Retention of Personal Information

We will retain your personal information in a form that identifies you only for as long as it serves the purpose(s) for which it was initially collected as stated in this Privacy Policy, subsequently authorized, or as allowed under applicable law.

### Delete Your Information

You may request access to and deletion of your personal data by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

### How We Protect Your Information

We take very seriously the security and privacy of the personal information that it collects pursuant to this Privacy Policy. Accordingly, we will implement reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, taking into account the risks involved in processing and the nature of such data, and comply with applicable laws and regulations.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through the Website or the Service. If you are under 13, please do not give us any personal information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide us Personal Information without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that personal information from our databases.

### External Websites

The Website may contain links to third party websites. Shortcut has no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors, or other websites to which we provide links. As such, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of those third party websites. You should check the applicable third party privacy policy and terms of use when visiting any other websites.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Website or notify you via e-mail, at our option, as soon as they go into effect. By using the Website, App or the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [\[email protected\]](https://shortcut.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍

‍

Build what’s next.

Experience the most enjoyable, powerful way for your team to work.

Alternatively, get in touch to [Request a Demo](https://shortcut.com/demo)

Features

Solutions

Learn

Resources

Company

© 2024 Shortcut Software Company
